{
    "id": "23aa3334fc2a420c9f6ba925c1ab5e35",
    "title": "Modal Auxiliaries",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I ate as much as I …………………………",
            "description": "We use could to show past ability.",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "could",
                "will"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "15cfc950064443048ef20a8d1a8d4ee6"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ………………………… walk when she was just eight months old.",
            "description": "We use could to show past ability.",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "could",
                "will"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c87402af16d04ce6829541046bf028e6"
        },
        {
            "question": "Shyam ……………………………… write with both hands. (present ability)",
            "description": "Can is used to talk about present ability. ",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "could",
                "would"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "24da611d32dc4dbd8bf3e99e32098622"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is confident that she ………………………….. get the job.",
            "description": "Will shows simple futurity. It is used to predict future. ",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "would",
                "could"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "cab2d751255d4abab0bc72503b6f2bff"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was sacked because he ……………………………. not meet the targets.",
            "description": "Either could or would can be used here with different meanings. Could not shows inability. Would not shows reluctance. ",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "can",
                "could"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "588b22a2dec24799a837009990a1cb84"
        },
        {
            "question": "She said that she ………………………….. come but she didn’t.",
            "description": "Would is the past tense of will in indirect speech.",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "will",
                "can"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "945e802a578142ca8aee4ac77113c27c"
        },
        {
            "question": "If I had more money, I ……………………………….. build a home.",
            "description": "Either could be used here with slightly different meanings. ",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "could",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "08e5b054daba42448c0759fb7ca0303f"
        },
        {
            "question": "If I were you, I …………………………… pay 2000 bucks for that used car.",
            "description": "Would not shows refusal. Could not shows inability. ",
            "answers": [
                "could not",
                "will not",
                "would not"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c3c6dcda8d36451b9c6935dddfd903a6"
        },
        {
            "question": "You ………………………….. visit me whenever you want.",
            "description": "Can is used to make a request, to ask for permission or to express ability to do something.",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "can",
                "could"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "207c802b572648e59ed0a42e0d837113"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who ……………………………. pay for the drinks?",
            "description": "Will is used to predict something, to express willingness or to announce a spontaneous decision. Can shows ability. ",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "can",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "ddbfea1a466748e7a9e67bb3db28db74"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………… you mind closing the door?",
            "description": "Would is used in polite requests.",
            "answers": [
                "Will",
                "Would",
                "Could"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "18f9af172a1b4fcba3c33d3d221b01c6"
        },
        {
            "question": "I wanted to scream but I …………………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "cannot",
                "couldn't",
                "won't"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8338853cbc044530932697cff94706c3"
        }
    ]
}